[

  {
    question: "Who wrote Harry Potter?",
    answers: {
      a: "JK Rowling",
      b: "Cressida Cowel",
      c: "Jake Rowling"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Harry's second son?",
    answers: {
      a: "Albus Severus Potter",
      b: "Severus Dumbledor Potter",
      c: "James Potter"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Who kills Nagini?",
    answers: {
      a: "Hermione Granger",
      b: "Neville Longbottom",
      c: "Harry Potter",
      d: "Luna Lovegood"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
{
  question: "What doe Madame Maxime tell Hagrid that her horses drink?",
  answers: {
    a: "Champagne",
    b: "Whiskey",
    c: "Ros√©",
    d: "Holy Water"
  },
  correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
  question: "What is Hermiones middle name?",
  answers: {
    a: "Jean",
    b: "Watson",
    c: "May",
    d: "Margaret"
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
  question: "What name does Hermione give when caught by the snatchers in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
  answers: {
    a: "Luna Lovegood",
    b: "Parvati Patel",
    c: "Penolope Clearwater",
    d: "Ginny Weasly"
  },
  correctAnswer: "c"
},
{
  question: "During which celebratory feast does Professor Quirrell inform everybody of a troll?",
  answers: {
    a: "Halloween",
    b: "Christmas",
    c: "Easter",
    d: "Valentines Day"
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},
{
  question: "What type of sweets does Bertie Bott make?",
  answers: {
    a: "Fizzing Whizpoppers",
    b: "Chocolate Frogs",
    c: "Every-flavour Jelly Babies",
    d: "Every-Flavour Beans"
  },
  correctAnswer: "d"
},
{
  question: "Which member of the Weasly family has his ear cursed off?",
  answers: {
    a: "Fred",
    b: "George",
    c: "Percy",
    d: "Arthur"
  },
  correctAnswer: "b"
},
{
  question: "How many staircases are their in Hogwarts?",
  answers: {
    a: "143",
    b: "153",
    c: "7",
    d: "1430"
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
}
];
